cloudonex.com 2018-04-17

# CloudOnex - Privacy Policy

**CloudOnex respects and values your need for online privacy. Therefore, we have established this Privacy Policy (referred to as the “Privacy Policy” herein) – so that we can unveil what information we collect about you and how we use, store and disclose such information. It is our obligation to help you make an informed decision about whether or not to share your information with us.**

_CloudOnex reserves the right to revise, modify, add or remove provisions to this Privacy Policy at any time. In the moment we do so, we will notify you in accordance with the notice provisions of our Terms of Service. Take note of the ‘Last Updated’ date listed at the foot of this Privacy Policy. If we make changes to this Privacy Policy, we will update that date to notify you of the date of such changes. By continuing to use the Website after receiving notice of the updated Privacy Policy, you acknowledge that you have read and understand the revised Privacy Policy._

#### How does CloudOnex collect information from you?

CloudOnex collects information from you when you send it to us directly by filling out forms on the Website (including any application you may make for Services or the Software), corresponding with us by e-mail, writing to us by post, or speaking to us by telephone. We also collect information from you when you browse the Website and use the Software, as set out in detail below. Some of the methods we use to collect data are automated and will take effect automatically as you navigate the Website and/or use the Software.

#### What information does CloudOnex collect?

**Personal Information.**

CloudOnex may collect information from you which may be personally identifiable such as names, addresses, telephone numbers, fax numbers, physical addresses, email addresses, credit card number (in the case of direct customers) and, if applicable, company names, addresses, telephone numbers, fax numbers, physical addresses, email addresses, credit card numbers or tax ID numbers as well as similar information concerning technical contacts, marketing contacts, and executive contacts within your company or organization (collectively, in formation of this nature shall be “Personal Information”).

**Non-Personal Information.**

CloudOnex may collect non-personally identifiable information from you such as the type of browser you use, your operating system, the screen resolution of your browser, your ISP, your IP address, which pages you view on the Site and the time and duration of your visits to the Site (collectively, “Non-Personal Information”). CloudOnex associates Non-Personal Information with Personal Information if you register with the Site.

**User Communications.**

If you communicate with us, we may collect information relating to that communication whether it takes the form of email, fax, letter, forum posting, testimonials or any other form of communication between you and CloudOnex or Submitted by you to the Site (collectively, “User Communications”).

**Usage Details**

Your usage details such as time, frequency, duration and pattern of use, features used and the amount of storage used will be recorded by us in order to enhance your experience of the CloudOnex Services and to help us provide you the best possible service.

**Contents of your User Account**

We store and maintain files, documents, to-do lists, emails and other data stored in your user account at our facilities in the United States. In order to prevent loss of data due to errors or system failures, we also keep backup copies of data including the contents of your user account. Hence your files and data may remain on our servers even after deletion or termination of your user account. We may retain and use your Personal Information and data as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our rights. We assure you that the contents of your user account will not be disclosed to anyone and will not be accessible even to employees of CloudOnex except in circumstances specifically mentioned in this Privacy Policy Statement and Terms of Services. We also do not scan the contents of your user account for serving targeted advertisements.

**Payment Information**

In case of services requiring payment, we request credit card or other payment account information, which will be used solely for processing payments. We will not store your financial information except for the name and address of the cardholder, the expiry date and the last four digits of the Credit Card number. Subject to your prior consent and where necessary for processing future payments, your financial information will be stored in encrypted form on secure servers of our reputed Payment Gateway Service Provider who is beholden to treating your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy Statement.

**Visitor Details**

We use the Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, files accessed, errors generated, time zone, operating system and other visitor details collected in our log files to analyze the trends, administer the website, track visitor's movements and to improve our website. We link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you.

**Server Information.**

If you use one of our software products such as our proprietary Web Hosting, Billing and Automation Solution, we may collect certain information concerning such software and concerning the server upon which the software operates. This information includes without limitation: (a) the licensed or unlicensed status of the software; (b) the source from which the license for the software was obtained (i.e., CloudOnex or a CloudOnex affiliate); or (c) information about the server upon which the software is installed including (i) the public IP address, (ii) the operating system and (iii) the use of any virtualization technologies on such server ((a) through (c) collectively, “Server Information”). Additionally, “Server Information” may also include (x) information collected by CloudOnex from time to time concerning which features of the software are most often used in order to improve and make adjustments to the software; and (y) information collected from you by CloudOnex in the event that you request technical support services including without limitation, IP addresses, usernames and passwords necessary to login to SSH, the root directory of the server upon which you installed the CloudOnex software and any affected accounts including email accounts, MySQL accounts and other accounts.

#### How does CloudOnex use and store the information it collects?

As a general matter, CloudOnex may use the information you disclose to us to improve and provide the Site, the Services and our other products and services, and for the specific purpose that you gave us the information. More specific details on how we use your information follow below.

We may use Personal Information to create and authenticate your account, to process transactions you request such as software license purchases, to provide you with the newsletters and mailing lists that you sign up for, to provide you with customer and technical support and to communicate with you about your account and our products and services. We may also use Personal Information to offer, market or advertise to you CloudOnex products and services. While such CloudOnex products and services may reference, incorporate or include third-party products and services, CloudOnex will not use your Personal Information to independently offer, market or advertise third-party products and services unless we first obtain your consent to do so. You may update your Personal Information with us, but we may maintain records of Personal Information you disclose to us indefinitely.

We may use User Communications in the same ways we use Personal Information. If you communicate with us for a particular purpose, we may use your User Communications for that purpose. For example, if you contact us for technical support, we may use your communications to provide technical support to you. We may maintain records of User Communications you transmit to us indefinitely.

CloudOnex may use Non-Personal Information to maintain, evaluate, improve and provide our Site, the Services and any other CloudOnex products and services. We may retain Non-Personal Information indefinitely.

We may use Server Information to provide you with technical support services and to maintain, evaluate, improve and provide CloudOnex products and services. We may also use such information to investigate unlicensed (and therefore unauthorized) uses of our software. CloudOnex may maintain Server Information indefinitely.

Where is your data stored?

Currently your data is stored in the US however, it may be transferred to different location and by accepting our terms of services and/or a software EULA, you are explicitly consenting to this transfer and storage taking place.

#### How does CloudOnex disclose the information it collects?

Except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy, CloudOnex does not share your Personal Information with unaffiliated third parties other than is set out in this Privacy Policy. CloudOnex will never disclose your Personal Information to an unaffiliated third party for the purposes of email or other marketing unless we first obtain your consent to do so.

CloudOnex cannot be responsible for protecting your information if you share such information in publicly available sections of the Site such as the user forums or testimonials section. You should use your own judgment in disclosing this information on the Site.

In the event that CloudOnex is purchased by another company, merges with another company or has a substantial portion of its assets purchased by another company, CloudOnex may share your information with that company. In such an event, we will notify you in accordance with the notice provisions of the Terms of Use.

We may share your information with third parties as permitted or required by Applicable Law, by a court order or by another judicial or governmental request. We may also disclose your information if we determine that such disclosure us necessary to protect CloudOnex’s rights and remedies or is necessary for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance. Such disclosures could take place in the context of an investigation or to prevent or take action against illegal activity, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of CloudOnex’s Terms of Service, applicable EULAs or other CloudOnex agreements, or as otherwise required by Applicable Law.

CloudOnex may disclose your information to affiliated third parties that assist us in providing maintaining, evaluating, improving and providing the Site, the Services and any other CloudOnex products and services. CloudOnex may disclose your information to affiliated third parties for the purposes of offering, marketing or advertising CloudOnex products and services to you (such CloudOnex products and services may reference, incorporate or include third-party products and services). In such an event, CloudOnex will take reasonable measures to prevent such affiliated third parties from using your information for other purposes.

#### Does CloudOnex use Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies?

Yes, CloudOnex uses temporary and permanent cookies to keep you logged in after you log in to the Site. Otherwise, you would have to log in again for each page of the Site that you visit.

Cookies are also used in Google Analytics tracking and for the tracking of referrals (if applicable).

Cookies are small text files placed on your computer by CloudOnex. They may be associated with your Personal Information by CloudOnex, but they do not contain your Personal Information. CloudOnex does not use web beacons.

We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as HTML 5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs.

Is CloudOnex responsible for the use or misuse of your information provided by you in the external links, contained in CloudOnex website?

Some pages of our website contain external links. You are advised to verify the privacy practices of such other websites. We are not responsible for the manner of use or misuse of information made available by you at such other websites. We encourage you not to provide Personal Information, without assuring yourselves of the Privacy Policy Statement of other websites.

#### How does CloudOnex protect Personal Information and other information about you?

CloudOnex takes reasonable steps to protect the information we collect about you. Additionally, we may supply you with tools to evaluate the strength of the password you select for the Site. No security measures are foolproof, and CloudOnex cannot guarantee the security of your information other than to take reasonable steps to protect it. In the event that CloudOnex becomes aware of a security breach, unauthorized disclosure or inadvertent disclosure concerning your information, you agree that CloudOnex may notify you of such an event using the notice provisions of the Terms of Use.

You are responsible for maintaining your account’s security (as more specifically explained in the Terms of Use).

**Federated Authentication**

You can log in to our site using federated authentication providers such as Facebook Connect. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain Personal Information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form.

**Investigation of Illegal Activity**

We may need to provide access to your Personal Information and the contents of your user account to our employees and service providers for the purpose of investigating any suspected illegal activity or potential violation of the terms and conditions for use of CloudOnex Services. However, CloudOnex will ensure that such access is in compliance with this Privacy Policy Statement and subject to appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

**Blogs and Forums**

We provide the capacity for users to post information in blogs and forums for sharing information in a public space on the website. This information is publicly available to all users of these forums and visitors to our website. We require registration to publish information, but given the public nature of both platforms, any Personal Information disclosed within these forums may be used to contact users with unsolicited messages. We encourage users to be cautious in disclosure of Personal Information in public forums, as CloudOnex is not responsible for the Personal Information users elect to disclose.

CloudOnex also supports third party widgets such as Facebook and Twitter buttons on the website that allow users to share articles and other information on different platforms. These widgets may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the widgets to function properly. These widgets do not collect or store any Personal Information from users on the website and simply act as a bridge for your convenience in sharing information. Your interactions with these widgets are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**Your Choice in Information Use**

In the event we decide to use your Personal Information for any purpose other than as stated in this Privacy Policy, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of your Personal Information for those other purposes. From time to time, we may send emails to you regarding new services, releases and upcoming events. You may opt out of receiving newsletters and other secondary messages from CloudOnex by selecting the ‘unsubscribe’ function present in every email we send. However, you will continue to receive essential transactional emails.

**Your Rights**

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at info[at] CloudOnex.com.

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

The Data Protection Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of $20 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

If you have any questions, comments or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at legal@cloudonex.com It is CloudOnex’s policy to investigate and attempt to resolve all formal written complaints we receive concerning this Privacy policy. CloudOnex will cooperate with appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between CloudOnex and an individual.
